Guide to the Eric Moe Collection, 1976- UA.90.F96
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Eric Moe Collection
1976
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Moe, Eric
UA.90.F96
13.9 Linear Feet (26 mss boxes plus 3 oversize boxes)
The Eric Moe Collection includes sketches, fair-copies, and computer-generated scores of the composer's works from the late 1970s to the present. Dr. Moe joined the music faculty at the University of Pittsburgh in 1989 as an Associate Professor, and was promoted to Full Professor in 1999.
Previous Citation
Eric Moe Collection, 1976-, UA.90.F96, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
The collection contains manuscripts and computer-generated scores of musical sketches and compositions by Moe, dated from 1976 and on. In some cases, compositions include individual pages that Moe revised during the composition process.
Materials are listed here and arranged chronologically by the year of composition. Because items were acquired at different times, some box numbers may appear out of sequence in the following Contents List.
Unless otherwise noted, there is one copy of each item listed.
Biography
Eric Moe (1954- ) is professor of Composition and Music Theory at the University of Pittsburgh, director of the University of Pittsburgh Electroacoustic Music Studio, and co-director of the Music on the Edge new music concert series. He studied composition at Princeton University (A.B.), and the University of California at Berkeley (M.A., Ph.D.). Moe founded the Ph.D. program in Composition/Theory in the Music Department at the University of Pittsburgh.
Moe was a founding member of EARPLAY, a new music ensemble based in San Francisco, CA. He is known as a composer and pianist and has received wide recognition for his work including the Lakond Award from the American Academy of Arts and Letters and a Guggenheim Fellowship. He has been commissioned by the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, the Fromm Foundation, the Koussevitzky Foundation, the Barlow Endowment, and Meet-the-Composer USA.
In addition, Moe earned fellowships from the Wellesley Composer's Conference and the Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, as well as residencies at the MacDowell Colony, Yaddo, Bellagio, the Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, the Millay Colony, the Ragdale Foundation, the Montana Artists Refuge, the Carson McCullers Center for Writers and Musicians, and the American Dance Festival.
From 1981 to 1989, he served on the faculty of the San Francisco State University, and also at the University of California, Santa Cruz (1980-1981). He holds the PhD (1982) and MA (1978) in composition from the University of California, Berkeley, and the A.B. in Music from Princeton University (1978).
Accruals
New material is expected to be donated on an ongoing basis.
Vocal music; Music -- United States -- 20th century; Composers -- United States; University of Pittsburgh; Faculty papers; Music; Music -- Manuscripts; Instrumental music; University of Pittsburgh -- Faculty; Moe, Eric -- Manuscripts; University of Pittsburgh. Music Department; Moe, Eric
- Conjunctions, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Scope and Content Notes
  Instrumentation: For Orchestra: Piccolo, 2 Flutes, 2 Oboes, English Horn, 2 Clarinets, 2 Bassoons, Contrabassoon, 4 Horns, 2 Trumpets (in C), 2 Trombones, Bass Trombone/Tuba, Timpani, Tom-Tom, Xylophone, Harp, 2 Violins, Violas, 'Celli, Contrbass.
  Dedication: Dedicated to Michael Senturia and the U.C. Berkeley Orchestra
  At end: "Berkeley, California 12/1/76"
  Notes: "Note: This piece was commissioned; one of the conditions was that it not exceed 2 minutes in length. hence the brevity of the work."
  - Full score. Ozalid-printed score. 9 pages., 1.
  - Full score. Ozalid-printed score. Spiral-bound. 9 pages., 2.
- A Pentamerous Piece, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Clarinet, Cello, Piano.
  Dedication: Edwin Dugger
  - Full score. Composer's ozalid draft with paste-over corrections on clarinet part (transposition) and crossed-out sections. Bound., 1.
  - Composer's ozalid draft with pencil corrections. Bound., 2.
  - Composer's ozalid draft with paste-over corrections, crossed-out sections, red marker corrections on cello part. Bound., 3.
  - Composer's ozalid holograph with no corrections. Bound. 5 copies., 4.
- Occasional Septet, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Flute, B-flat bass clarinet, B-flat trumpet, Vibraphone/Piano, Violin, Viola, Violoncello
  Dedication: Walter Winslow
  Note: Subtitle: Swirls to Pine.
  - Flute part (unlabeled). Composer's ozalid score., 1.
  - B-flat bass clarinet part. Composer's ozalid score., 2.
  - B-flat trumpet part. Composer's ozalid score., 3.
  - Vibraphone/piano part. Composer's ozalid score., 4.
  - Violin part. Composer's ozalid score., 5.
  - Viola part (unlabeled). Composer's ozalid score., 6.
  - 'Cello part. Composer's ozalid score., 7.
  - Full score. Composer's ozalid draft with paste-over correction and pencil corrections., 8.
  - Full score. Composer's ozalid draft with pencil corrections & list of errata written on back cover., 9.
  - Full score. Composer's ozalid score with no corrections. 2 copies., 10.
- Etude, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Cello
  Dedication: Cathy Allen
  At end: "12/2/79"
  Notes: Subtitle: Hommage à S. Beckmesser
  - Cello part. Composer's holograph with title caption and performance notes placed at bottom of pages. 5 copies., 1.
  - Cello part. Composer's holograph with title page and performance notes page. Missing page 4. 1 copy., 2.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 22 leaves. 9 blank., 3.
- Four Elizabethan Lyrics, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Violin, Viola, Horn in F sharp, Bassoon, Harp, Guitar, Piano
  Dedication: Dedicated, with gratitude, to Claudio Spies At end: I. "Berkeley, CA 3/21/79" III. "7/6/79 Berkeley, California on my father's 50th birthday" IV. "March 13, 1980/Berkeley, California"
  Notes: Four movements: I. They free from me, based on text by Sir Thomas Wyatt. (Instruments: violin, viola, horn in F, bassoon, soprano, harp, guitar and piano). II. The Madman's Song, based on text by John Webster. (Instruments: violin, horn, voice and piano.) III. Slow, Slow, Fresh Fount, based on text by Ben Jonson. (Instruments: voice, harp, guitar and piano.) IV. Queen and Huntress, based on text by Ben Jonson. (Instruments: violin, viola, horn, bassoon, mezzo soprano, harp, guitar and piano.)
  - Violin part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 1.
  - Viola part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 2.
  - Horn in F sharp part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 3.
  - Bassoon part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 4.
  - Bassoon part. Composer's holograph on ozalid., 5.
  - Harp part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 6.
  - Guitar part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 7.
  - Piano part. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 8.
  - Sketches for movements I to III. Composer's holograph on yellow staff paper., 9.
  - Full score. Drafts for movements I to IV. Composer's holograph on yellow staff `, 10.
  - Photocopy of autograph manuscript score of "Slow, Slow Fresh Fount" with pen and pencil corrections. 21 pages. 3 copies, 1 with corrections for each instrument (voice, viola, piano)., 11.
  - Photocopy of autograph manuscript score. 51 pages. 4 copies., 1. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph with pencil corrections. 51 pages., 1. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript score., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript score. Composer's name pasted over. Time durations of each piece written in pen. Includes pencil notations.., 3.
  - Full score. Ozalid score with pencil corrections. 51 pages., 4.
- Kesa and Morito, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Piccolo, 2 Flutes, 1 Alto Flute, 2 Oboes, 1 English Horn, 2 Clarinets in B-flat (1 also in E-flat), 1 Bass Clarinet, 2 Bassoons, 1 Contrabassoon, 4 Horns, 2 Trumpets in B-flat, 2 Trombones (tenor and bass), 1 Tuba, 12 or more 1st Violins, 12 or more 2nd Violins, 8 or more Violas, 8 or more Violoncellos, 4 or more Contra-Basses (at least 2 with C extension), Percussion.
  Dedication: "for our parents"
  Notes: Libretto by Keith Moe, after story by Ryunosuke Akutagawa.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. 60 pages., 1.
  - Full score. Composer's holograph on ozalid. Spiral bound., 1. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Fantasy, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript score. Includes Performance Notes page. 5 copies., 1.
  - Copy of autograph manuscript score. 19 leaves. 2 copies., 2.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript score. 20 leaves (last one blank), 3.
- The Sacrifice of Iphigenia (Chorus after Aeschylus), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Chorus, 2 trumpets in C, 2 horns, 2 trombones (tenor and bass), tuba, pianoforte and percussion.
  At end: "rev. 11/1984 Rome-San Francisco"
  - Autograph manuscript score. Final manuscript. Signed at end. 33 leaves., 1.
  - Photocopy of autograph manuscript score. 33 pages., 1. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Bound photocopy of autograph manuscript score. 33 pages., 2.
- Siegfried Idyll, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Piano. Arranged for 4 hands.
  At end: "EHM arr. Rome/San Francisco 8/23/84"
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript score. 27 leaves. 5 blank., 1.
- Songs Not So Serious, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Instrumentation: Voice, piano.
  Dedication: for Anna Carol Dudley
  At end: "12/20/1984 Rome/San Francisco"
  Notes: Subtitle: "On Poems of William Carlos Williams." Four movements: I. from "Three Nahuatl Poems;" II. Sonnet in Search of an Author; III. Song; IV. Portrait of a Lady
  - Full score. Copy of autograph holograph score. Includes texts of the poems. 2 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph holograph score. 2 copies., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph holograph score. Includes pencil corrections. 24 pages., 3.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript score., 4.; 26 leaves. 2 blank.
- Variations for Violoncello and Piano, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Violoncello, Piano
  Dedication: for Laszlo Varga
  At end: "San Francisco 3/1/1985"
  - Full score. Copy of composer's score. Spiral bound. Labeled "rev.", 1985; 1.
    No Subnote Content
  - Full score. Copy of composer's score. One labeled "unrevised;" one labeled "old" with composer's name cut out of cover page & crossed out on first page; one labeled "old, w/revisions in pencil." 3 copies., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of composer's ozalid score on regular staff paper. 2 copies., 1. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Violoncello part. Copy of composer's holograph. 2 copies., 2.
  - Autograph manuscript of theme & sketches., 3.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. Signed at end. Includes paste-overs. 36 leaves., 4.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript/copied holograph. Includes paste-overs. Note at top: "additional/alternate bowings and fingerings by Laszlo Varga")., 5.
  - Reel-to-reel tape recording., 1. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    a. "Recorded 3/9/1986, Kurth Hall"—Container.
- A Whirling and a Wandering Fire, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Flute, B-flat clarinet (doubling Bass Clarinet), Piano
  Dedication: for Janet Kutulas and Peter Josheff
  At end: "I/1986 San Francisco"
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Spiral bound. 4 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Spiral bound. Has corrections in pencil and marker. Labeled "Lolly's notes.", 2.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. 32 leaves., 3.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 4.
  - Full score. Paste-overs & revisions to select pages., 5.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript draft. Pencil notations. Found in envelope labeled "performance copy - piano.", 6.
  - DAT tapes with this composition's name on label. 3 copies., 7/2/97; 7.
  - Letter from recording studio with recording notes and marked score., 8.
- Byzantium, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Flute (doubling Piccolo), B-flat Clarinet (doubling Bass Clarinet), B-flat Trumpet, Violin, Violoncello, Contrabass, Baritone, Piano, Percussion.
  Dedication: for Allen Shearer
  At end: "San Francisco – January 1987"
  Note: Based on text by W.B. Yeats
  - Text of poem with notes., 1.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 3 copies., 1. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. In envelope labeled "master.", 2.
  - Errata sheet., 3.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Spiral bound. Includes performance notes and text by W. B. Yeats. 3 copies., 1. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Spiral bound. Has measure letters added in blue marker; includes performance notes and text by W. B. Yeats, 1. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. Spiral bound. Includes performance notes and text by W.B. Yeats., 2.
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. Includes paste-overs. Signed at end. 64 leaves., 1. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript draft. Corrections in red pencil; Includes performance notes & text by W.B. Yeats., 2.
  - Piano reduction. Copy of autograph manuscript draft. Corrections in pencil., 3.
- Auto Songs/Dances, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: [Electroacoustic, FM Synthesis.]
  Note: Published as "Songs and Dances of the Automobile: I. Mambo. II. Nocturne. III. 5 Piston Fling."
  - Autograph sketches. In envelope labeled "presto" with additional 4 pages of notes. 4 pages., 1.
  - Autograph sketches. In envelope labeled "ballad" with additional 4 pages of notes. 5 pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer generated holograph. 9 pages., 3.
  - Autograph sketches. 5 pages., 4.
  - Computer-generated notes. 9 pages., 5.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 10 pages., 6.
  - Computer printout and pencil notes. 7 pages., 7.
- Off Trail, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: 2 Flutes (1 Piccolo), 2 Oboes, 2 Clarinets in B-flat, 1 Bass Clarinet, 2 Bassoons, 4 Horns, 2 Trumpets in C, 2 Tenor/Bass Trombones, 1 Bass Trombone, 1 Tuba, Percussion, Harp, Piano, Violin I & II, Viola, Violoncello, Contrabass.
  Dedication: For David Sloss and the Fremont-Newark Philharmonic
  At end: "11/25/1988 MacDowell Colony"
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 83 pages. Spiral bound. 6 copies. Not bound. 1 copy., 1.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 83 pages. 11 x 17. No title page., 1. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Copy of autograph manuscript draft. 83 pages. Spiral bound. Handwritten note on cover: "unrevised." 2 copies., 1. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Copy of manuscript score. 83 pages. Spiral bound. 2 copies., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript draft. 83 leaves. Labeled "Revised Master." Spiral bound. Pen and pencil corrections., 1. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript score. 83 leaves. 2 copies., 2.
  - Individual parts for Bass Clarinet in B-flat, Harp, Piano, Flutes 1 and 2, Oboes 1 and 2, Clarinets 1 and 2 in B-flat, Bassoon 1 and 2, Trumpets 1 and 2 in C, Horns I and III in F, Horns II and IV in F, Trombones 1 and 2, Trombone 3 (Tuba) and Percussion, Violin I, Violin II, Viola, Cello. Autograph manuscript holograph. Includes paste-overs., 1. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 46 leaves (12 blank). Sketches on the back sides of pages are crossed off., 1. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. 1 leaf (recto blank, verso music crossed off) and 83 leaves. 1 errata sheet in pencil., 1. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Photocopy of autograph manuscript score. 83 leaves. Spiral-bound., 2.
- Up & At 'Em, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Alto Flute, English Horn, Bass Clarinet, Viola, Piano.
  Dedication: For the Serge Koussevitzky Music Foundation in the Library of Congress, and dedicated to the memory of Serge and Natalie Koussevitzky
  At end: "12/7/1988 MacDowell Colony"
  Dedication: for Carolyn Forman Moe
  Notes: Three movements. I. Up; II. &; III. At 'Em.
  - Autograph manuscript draft. Movement III. 18 leaves, 9 with draft, 9 with music crossed out., 1.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript draft. 38 pages. Includes pen and pencil corrections., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript draft. 38 pages. Includes pencil notations, possibly performer notes. Includes paste overs., 3.
  - Full score. Copy of printed score. Pencil notes & corrections. Errata listed on cover page., 4.
  - Full score. Copy of printed score., 5.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. With highlighter and pencil notes, possibly for performance. Includes paste-overs and some notes whited-out., 6.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 77 pages. 2 copies., 7.
  - Individual parts for Bass clarinet (8 pages), English horn (6 pages), Viola (8 pages), Alto Flute (8 pages, last one blank). Autograph manuscript holograph. A different version of Viola/page 6 is also included, plus 3 copied pages of an alternate Viola score. Note on envelope: "beware: page 5 & 6 of both E. horn and viola part are reversed on original.", 8.
  - Full score. Copy of computer-generated score. 77 pages. Spiral bound. Handwritten note on cover: "VCL edit.", 1. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Alto flute part. Copy of computer-generated score. 11 pages. Spiral bound., 2.
  - English horn part. Copy of computer-generated score. 10 pages. Spiral bound., 3.
  - Bass clarinet part. Copy of computer-generated score. 13 pages. Spiral bound., 4.
  - Viola part. Copy of computer-generated score.17 pages. Spiral bound., 5.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript score. 38 pages. Spiral bound. Includes pen and pencil corrections and paste overs., 6.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript score. 38 pages. Includes pen and pencil corrections and paste-overs., 7.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 11" x 17" paper., 1. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 11" x 17" paper. Pages 1 and 21 only., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 11" x 17" paper. Pages 1 and 10 only., 3.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 11" x 17" paper. Some notes whited out., 4.
- Riprap, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Cello, Piano, Percussion.
  Dedication: for John Swackhamer
  At end: "10/7/1989 S.F./Pgh."
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. Includes instrumentation and performance notes. Spiral bound. 5 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. In envelope labeled "Riprap master.", 1. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 37 pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 75 pages., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 38 pages. 2 copies., 4.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 38 pages. Has pencil notations, possibly performance notes., 5.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 38 pages. Has red pencil notations, possibly performance notes., 6.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 33 pages. Spiral bound. 2 copies., 1. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Full score. Autograph manuscript holograph. 17 leaves., 1. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Autograph manuscript sketches., 2.
  - Full score. Copy of autograph manuscript holograph. 35 pages., 3.
- Sonatuna, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: B-flat Clarinet, String Quartet.
  Dedication: Commissioned by and dedicated to the amateur musicians of the Wellesley Composers' Conference
  - Concert program. The New Music Group. November 7, 1991., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 45 pages. Spiral bound. 2 copies., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 48 pages, 1 blank., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. Pencil notations. 2 copies., 4.
- The Trojan Women, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Electroacoustic music.
  Note: Incidental music for play performed October 12, 1990, at Southern Illinois University at Carbondale. Director was Christian Moe.
  - TX802 and DX7 II computer printout. 2 pages., 1.
  - Handwritten notes. Pen and pencil. 8 pages., 2.
  - Daily Egyptian newspaper article, October 12, 1990., 3.
  - Computer printed verse for play. Pencil notes. 18 pages., 4.
  - Rehearsal schedule. 2 pages., 5.
  - Music scheme. Pen and pencil corrections. 6 pages., 6.
  - Copy of "The Trojan Women" Lattimore translation. 23 pages., 7.
  - Copy of "Women of Troy" by Frederick Williams. Stage play. 38 pages. Pencil notes., 8.
  - Copy of "Women of Troy" by Frederick Williams. Stage play. 38 pages. Spiral bound. Pencil notes., 9.
  - Autograph manuscript sketches. 12 leaves (7 blank)., 10.
- O Vos Omnes, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Soprano, Alto, Tenor, Bass
  Dedication: for John Goldsmith and the Bellefield Singers
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. 10 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 2 copies., 1991; 2.
- We Happy Few, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Violin, Cello, Piano.
  Dedication: for the Washington Square Contemporary Music Society
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Includes performance notes page. Spiral bound. 5 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. Note on cover: "rec. session edits 11/3/97" and pencil notations on score. Includes notes pages., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 3 copies., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Pencil notations throughout., 4.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. In envelope labeled "WHF master." 3 copies., 5.
  - Cello part. Computer-generated scpre. Spiral bound., 6.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 27 pages. Pasted into artist's sketchbook. On cover is written "violin." Pen and pencil notations., 1. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. 25 pages. Pasted into artist's sketchbook. On cover is written "cello" Pen and pencil notations., 2.
- Grande Etude Brilliante, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Piano.
  Dedication: for Alan Feinberg
  - Piano score. Computer-generated score. Includes performance notes. 1 spiral-bound copy; 5 additional non-bound copies., 1.
- Sad Steps, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: Oboe and piano.
  Dedication: for Marcia Butler
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. Includes performance notes. 2 copies., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Includes performance notes., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score., 3.
  - Recording notes dated 3/2/95., 4.
- On the Tip of My Tongue, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Instrumentation: Bass Clarinet and Keyboard Synthesizer (Yamaha DX7 with TX802 tone generator).
  Dedication: for Tim Smith
  Commission: Commissioned by Tim Smith
  Note: Four movements: I. Two-part Contraption; II. Tim's Tune; III. Double Take; IV. What the Drums Say.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. Includes drum tuning for 4th movement and performance notes. Note on cover: "rec. editing" with pencil notations on score and editing notes tucked into score., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Spiral bound. Includes drum tuning for 4th movement and performance notes. 3 copies., 2.
  - Full score, 4th movement. Computer-generated score. Includes drum tuning., 3.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score pasted onto sheets. 23 pages (missing page 5)., 4.
  - Extra pages that appear to be from the same score. Published score is 39 pages., 5.
  - Concert program from Feb. 6, 1993, that includes "Tip of My Tongue." Pomona College., 6.
  - Full score. Computer-generated score. Possibly performance score due to handwritten notes., 7.
- Fancy Footwork, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)